Hello everyone!
This is Hitomi Takamatsu from Equal Love!
Yes! That's right!
It's Equal Love Boat Racing Club today!
Ta-da! Look! Hoodies are ready!
We made a T-shirt and now we have a hoodie!
It's so cute!
So, here it is!
What a surprise today!
I'll tell you which boat race track I'm at.
What a surprise!
We are at a boat race track in Korea!
Why?
Look! Look! It's a light boat! I didn't know there was a boat race track in Korea? I'm sure you're wondering.
But it looks like this is the only one, so thank you very much for letting me come here!
Hello!
I am really surprised at myself, because before ECO NO IJOY 2023
I was a winner of the ECO NO IJOY 2023 live broadcast with some of the ECO NO IJOY members.
I was a little bit surprised at myself, because I won the live distribution with some members of ECO NO IJOY before the ECO NO IJOY 2023.
I was the only one who came to the boat race in Korea alone! Thank you very much for your kindness.
Thank you very much!
I'm still a little bit confused about everything.
It seems that there are some races and ways to buy boats that are different from Japan's system.
I'm going to have a lot of fun today!
I don't think I have any information on Korean boat racecourses yet.
I hope you will watch this video as a reference!
Oh my god! Boats! I can hear the sound of engines!
I'm off!
Yes!
So, we'll start with the 11th race, and this is the display. Display? Then, starting from the 11th race, this is the exhibition. Display?
Let's take a look at the turn here.
It's no different from boat races in Japan.
It's good!
What?
What should I do? Isn't it a people-watching race?
Where do I start? Should we try to buy that "three-piece dress"? Three-piece clothing is an original Korean way of buying.
It is a combination of three pieces of clothes and three pieces of clothing.
Does that mean I get one piece of clothing and two pieces of clothing? Two of them are clothes, right?
Then I'll buy that one called 3 single clothes.
This 11 Ruth 3 is the most expected to come.
It's like pupil Ruth with 1.
I think I'll go with one and three.
I can only buy the three in a row by voting online.
I can't buy three in a row today.
I'm looking at two eyes in a row right now.
No, I don't know.
I'm going to buy two pairs of eyes.
It's the most popular.
4.7.
I'll buy 500 yen...
How much are we going to spend today?
100,000 won
I have to use up 10,000 won 10,000 yen
Once 500 yen
500 yen for an eye
3 single clothes to make one 3,4
Yes, done.
OK, let's go home. OK, let's go home.
Debut in Korea
I bought one of the most popular ones in Korea.
I'm not going to play God in Korea, but...
I'm just happy to win.
50,000 won.
Five thousand yen.
Khamo-samnita.
Are you going home so early?
He's leaving.
He's right. He's at the window. And he's out in one second.
Race 11, 134. Three repetitions.
One-three in a row.
Five hundred.
He changed it.
I changed it, so it's okay.
It's a big deal that your bodyguard is here, but...
Thank you very much.
A little bit of Korean.
I know a few words.
Oh, hey there, Chokun.
Chokun...
That's 15,000 won, 1,500 yen.
One 34 triple and one 13 double.
I'm having fun.
What?
It's a little bit dangerous to be in a Mortal Race in a very foreign country.
But don't worry, folks.
The staff made this for me.
I don't know what's written here...Something about where this is written and what it says.
If you take these things with you, you can write the mark sheets right away.
You can get in right away.
The admission fee...
The admission fee is...
The admission fee is 1000 won.
The admission fee is 1000 won, which is about 100 yen.
Anyone can enter if they pay it.
You can also buy books like this one in Japan.
It's okay if you look at it while you're doing it.
Oh no!
Race 11 is about to start!
I saw an inn.
Are there people making noise?
Is it just me?
The G1 race is about to begin!
Here comes the G1 race!
I want to show it in Korea!
Looks like it's going to be me.
Let's go!
Hi Ting!
One will finish you this day!
Three is coming! Why?
Four's good, four's coming!
Oh, no! Wait, four? Oh, my God.
One!
Oh, wait!
Whoa!
Aah!Aah!
Why?
Oh, no! Oh, no! I'm so depressed!
What's Otz? Otz!
One, six, two.
I think this one's gonna work.
I've got it!
I owe you 1,500 yen!
162 times!
The inside got away, didn't it?
It's A2, the first boat.
Oh, but they're still competing. But they're still competing.
They're still competing on the second lap.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Oh, 4 is good!
Four, four, four!
I got it!
Oh!
Oh, my God! I should've gone with the six.
Choc! Oh, my God.
I should've picked 1, 4, and 6 in 3 singlets.
I'd have won, right?
I'm very disappointed.
It's so frustrating.
Unlike Japan.
Maybe no one shouts so loud.
Or me.
Calm?
Boat racecourses in Korea are very calm.
I was a little upset at first.I was a little bit furious at first.
I'll do my best.
I'm here at the concession stand, and I'd like to have a meal at a Korean concession stand.
What, one of these two kinds?
Ramen or Chanchi Guksu?
Okay, I'll order.
Ah!
I bought it! He gave me my change.
Oh, wow!
Kamasan bought two tiers, too.
Well, I'd like to go now.
I bought both ramen and udon!
I'm full.
Looks so good! It smells so good!
Is it spicy?
Oh, wow! There's kimchi!
It's a Korean recipe.
It's a normal Korean dish.
Here is Ramen
Here is Kimchi Books!
Kimchi is self-serve and comes with rice!
Amazing!
I really want to win after this.
I want to build up my strength!
Bon appétit!
I can say "Bon appétit!
Kira!
Bon appétit!
From the soup!From the soup!
Delicious!
Just right!
Not too thick, not too thick.
It's delicious!
Bon appétit!
Masissa!
It's so mashissa!
Delicious!
It's really like Japanese noodles!
It's like udon noodles with white broth.
Now on to the next one...
Ramen!
I'm finding out that I can't eat this!
Because it's spicy ramen!
This is spicy ramen!
Spicy ramen, really spicy?
Bon appétit!
Spicy ramen
Spicy, spicy, spicy, spicy, spicy, spicy
Then let's all enjoy it together
Let me know if it looks good.
A little sour type of kimchi
Not too spicy
It's not from the station in Japan, but it's a little spicy
Real kimchi
I'll eat it!
Delicious!
I've always dreamed of eating rice with a long Korean spoon!
I think I'll try noodles too!I think I'll just try the noodles too.
The soup is spicy.
I like noodles.
Noodles are delicious.
If you come to the boat race track
I hope you'll try these two.
Please eat them!
Thanks for the food!
In Korean
Good bye.
Now, do you want to go win?
Sero again.
I want to win!
I'll do my best!
Reserved seats?
Reserved seats.
Oh, are you sure? Here.
Can you show me to my reserved seat?
They're treating us really well.
What's going on?
12 minutes to race 13.
Let's get to it.
All right, let's get race 13 underway.
I like the third boat.
Race 13 will be one, two, three, four.
I, for one, believe this, today.
I'm going to live by this strategy, this book.
I'm going to live by it, today.
What's with the pen, too?
Mackie.Macky.
Not Mackie.
Yes, it's Mackie.
I think two pencils would be better.
And, you know, with the pencils, it's so hard to do it with a pencil, so...
This is good.
One, two, one, four looks good.
I've got a real hunch.
Just say the number you want.
I'm off.
I'm used to it by now.
I'm a pro. I'm a pro at the Korean boat race.
I'm a pro.
The buy tickets for the 13 races.
500 yen each.
1,500 yen, all in all.
the clothes on the table
One, two, four and one, two, three
And 2, 1, 4.
Rather. Maybe this is a hard race.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know, but I think it's a solid race, so
I think we're gonna win this one.
Isn't it great?
It's a mark sheet.
And this one here, canjon, it means "agreement.
It means "agreement.
So check here.
Check the race number.
And there are 1, 2, and 3 types. So, one, two, three types.
3 on one this mark sheet
You can do it for three different
You have to write down the types here, the 2-way and the 3-way.
You have to write them down in advance.
Fill in what you want to buy with what you wrote down.
If I buy 1, 2, and 4, then
1, 2, 4, 1, 2, 4, 1, 2, 4, 1, 2, 4, 1, 2, 4, 1, 4
1, 2, 4, 1, 4, 2, 3 single clothes I could buy
And here's the thing.
Well, you can buy something here for as little as 10
You can buy from 100 won, from 10 yen.
I heard that you can only buy up to 10,000 yen, for one race.
Then, you take the cash and go to buy.
Then, you just peep peep, and this comes out in one second.
I'm hoping to win 13 races like this.
I don't know much about how to read OOTS.
I don't know much about how to read otts, so I'll just use this book.
Hitokichi-san is doing his best to watch it.
I hope this video will help those who are interested in Korean boat racecourses
I hope this video can help those who are interested in Korean boat races.
I hope this video will be of some help to those who are interested in Korean boat race tracks.
I hope this video will be of some help to those who are interested in boat racing in Korea.
I hope you understand what I'm saying.
It's difficult, isn't it?
But once I bought one race at a time
I was already familiar with it.
I'm sure you will be able to apply it right away.
Boat racecourses in Korea also have seats like this.
There are seats outside and inside.It's outside, it's inside, and it's not so different from Japan.
It's not so different from Japan, after all.
And the last two races, from the moment you leave the pit
So it's a chaos situation boat race.
That's the online start race.
What's that? What does that mean?
You start with a unique child.
Then deaths start, then 10,000.
Isn't that dangerous?
It's kind of scary.
Race 13 is about to begin.
Oh, wow.
There are 6 boats, and the colors of boats 1 to 6 are exactly the same as in Japan, so it's very easy to understand.
And the ranks, from A1 to B2.
The ranks are also very easy to understand.
If 56 don't show up, it'll be good. Please.
I don't know how much it costs to buy 500 yen, or how to look at it.
I don't know how to read Tsugawa.
Here we go. Race 13 is underway.
Kenti, there's someone here who hasn't been home yet.
Dare, come to the right and get lost.
I'll see you later.
I'll be right behind you.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I'll be right back.
Garry Kei.
Gyfry
Garry Kei Gyfry
First time hitting a bullseye, right?
Yes! Yes!
What, 124?
You can win 124!
Oh! Oh, it's gone. It's gone.
Wait a minute.
Yasa Х
Ayasa H.
Three in one suit.
One person...
Yasaha, λέ was 500 yen.
He's waving!
Kamsahamnida!
Yay!
It was so popular, wasn't it?
I'll tell you what.
I'll let Dad know.
Then I'd like to pay you back.
I wonder how much.
Yay!
Let's see.
Forty thousand.
500 won.
That means 4,050 yen. 4,050 yen returned. I didn't bite at all. But I spent 1,500 yen on the current race, so I got back more than double.
Thank you. I'm doing well. All right, all right, let's go for it. Let's go for it.
The next race is race 14. My target is 1326.
I'm getting it right.
The boat No. 4 with the rice seal came in race 13.
And in Race 11, which I mentioned earlier, the No. 6 boat with the rice seal also came.
So, I believe in this rice seal. So I manage to believe in this rice seal.
I believe this is a larval figure.
So the next, er, so the next 14 races, this person was a woman.
So it has a rice seal, and I'd like to buy it with a little bit of involvement.
Then I would like to predict the 14th race.
Race 14.
Canjan.
I'm already going to be a three-bearing-clothes woman.
Wow, 26 women.
Isn't your motor winning percentage 6, 6?
I'm 6th. 6 is coming.
I'll buy it when it's around 6.
Seven minutes ago, seven minutes ago.
She's early.
Really early.
Okay, I'll buy it.
I'll give it to him like this, and he'll receive it.
Thank you for the food.
I bought it.
Can.
This is my buy for the 14 races. I bought 1,200 yen in total this time.
First, 3-barrels of 126, 3-barrels of 136, and 3-barrels of 326 for 3 atawas.
If this comes, it looks a little bit bad, so once it comes, it will be 200 yen.
I think it will come around here.
But so far it's not popular in order.
This is coming to 3,000 yen, so it's kind of very rough.
I bought it in order because I don't have an image that it is rougher than Japan.
This is the one the staff bought,
Then what are you doing, seriously.Then what are you doing, seriously.
Amazing.
236, 236, 6, 123, 123, 123, 30,500 each.
When this comes in, you're buying 3,000 yen?
You're buying 3,000 yen for six.
We need to decide how many of these boats we're going to leave.
That's right.
It's the cheapest.
This one seems to be coming.
And you're buying 3,000 yen.
You're right.
Let's get preliminary and go home.
It's starting.
Please, please.
Please let me win.
Please.
I wonder if Korea also changes new entrants.
I wonder if the basic entry number is 123456.
In the 14th race this time, the second boat and the sixth boat are female, so I'm calling 26.
I'm putting on 26.
I want to be as excited as all of you. I want to be as excited as you are.
I want to be as excited as you.
Race 14 is about to start.
Fighty, fighty, fighty.
Six good.
3 are coming. 3 are coming. 3 are coming. 3 are coming.
3 coming. 6 coming.
6 coming, 6 coming, 6 coming.
6 coming in for a touch.Six coming in a touch.
One, six?
Yeah.
Three's okay.
I got it. I got it. I'm right.
Four.
Six.
Six, six, six, six, six, six.
One, six.
Eh, it's working.
One, six, three.
Oh, no.
Don't come in, 4.
3 coming!
But it's going to be 3. 1, 3, 6. 1, 3, 6.
I'm doing good. It's okay. You're doing good. You're doing good.
I've already kicked it. I kicked it. Go, go, go!
Oh, no.
There's only 136 yen left. Look. We've only got 136 yen left.
16, go 6, go 6, go 6, go 6! Come on, 66666666!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Three!
I got it!
Four!
I bought it!
Is this the Korean guy?
I wonder if I'm Korean?
Maybe the Koreans are doing it.
136 yen136 yen.
I think you got your money back, didn't you?
I'm sure you did.
I paid 500 yen for it.
163 yen. That's delicious.
I'm having as much fun with you guys as I did with you.
I'm having just as much fun with you guys today.
I really won!
It's 1,314 yen.
$1,314.
I'm so happy!
Thank you very much.
I've won a lot of money buying popular items.
It's a Korean boat.
It's a Korean boat, sir.
Then let's go to the refund together.
I'll see you later, Buchan.
I'll be back, Buchan.
You're the best, Buchan.
How strong?
How's it going?
Seino!
8,500 yen!
Yes!
We got it!
I got 10,000 yen out of it, 12,000 yen for beating the other guy.
We won!
We're in the black again today!
Thank you very much.
I'll take the staff's hand.I'll take the staff's hand.
How much was it, Mr. Watts?
About twice as much as before.
170,000 won. That's 17,000 yen.
Thank you very much.
It's back.
500 yen.
That's 80,000 won.
That's 8,500 won.
It's back.
If you add it up with what you just got back...
It comes to 120,050 won.
So it comes to 120,500 won
Since it will be 120,500 won
That's 12,000 won.
I already have 12,000 won on hand.
So I'm in the plus column today.
Thank you very much.
Plus race!
Let's go home.
I don't want to do it anymore.
We're in the plus column.
Yes!
Let's go live in Korea.
Let's really go live in Korea.
Okay.
Now that we're on the right track...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's keep going.
And race 15.
Okay, I'd like to make a prediction for race 15.
You're predicted to come to the nearer.
One, two, three, six.
Oh, it's the same as before.
The third boat in race 15 is a woman.
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Wow, that's a strong boat, number 6.
She's got a good motor.
I'm interested in the fifth boat.
Two big ones.
Yeah, she is.
But they're all in two.
But maybe the second boat is stronger.
Two to go.
Two more and I'm still in it.
I haven't spent all 10,000 yet.
I've only spent 4,200 yen.
Just in time!
I'm back.
Race 15.
Two horses, second place, junior high.
Three suits of 136.
Three in 136.
And I was wondering something.
But I only paid $100 for it.
I don't know if it's popular.
But it doesn't matter to me anymore.
I'm buying it.
I already bought a good one.
So it's just for fun.
It's the first time I feel at ease.
For the first time in the Rotoracing Club, I feel at ease.
I'm going to enjoy it.
So I'll enjoy it... and I'll start with Starstar's buy-in.
Two.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Two, three, five. Two, three, five.
Two, one, three, one, three.
Oh, my goodness, we're gonna win this. We're gonna win it.
We're gonna win this one together.
We're gonna win!
You can hear it now.
No, no, no.
No, you're going to win.
You're going to win!
I'm so happy I'm telling my dad all about it.
I'm reporting everything to my father.
Is he interested, too?
Yeah, he's curious about the Korean boat race track.
I don't want a souvenir of some kind, so he can tell me how to get in here.
Just that souvenir story.
Here we go... the liberalization race.
No, I've never won anything like this.No, I've never been so lucky.
It's fun.
It's fun. It's fun when you hit it.
I didn't know.
You don't know the joy of winning.
Boat racing is a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
It's fun.
It's still fun.
Fifteen in a row.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Gunga Gunga.
Is anyone asking for it or not?
Fighting
Oh, shit. Two coming.
Two coming, two coming, two coming, two coming, two coming, two coming.
Two... two... two for sure.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. You're not flying or something, are you?
Right head, right head.
Wow, that's tough.
Tough.
Wow, you've got to get a six.
I'd like to see a six come in on a three.
So you might want the six to pass the three.
Wow.
No.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I can go 6, I can go 6, I can go 6.
26, 26, 26, 26...
Actually, it's the first one. It's anticipated.Actually, it's the first one, so this is anticipated
Why belong?
No... yes...
booboo
Four hits.
Jonathan
Wow, that's frustrating. 2, 1, 3.
Are you looking at the next exhibit?
Oh, let's see the exhibit.
Oh, my gosh.
This, this is really a matter of energy.
The motors.
This is great.
So it's a motor, right?
It's a motor.
Once it starts, it's a straight line.
It's a start.
We're going to start from the pit.
That's interesting.
Who's the favorite in this one?
Hand #5?
Two, three, four, five.
This is some kind of ranking.
The motor in hand 5 is fine.
And better?
But 4 has to have some kind of technology, because it's A1.
I don't know. I don't know. It's too much of a game of luck.
But, yeah, I think the stronger the motor, the better.
Sashiko. Sashiko.
Sashiko.
Sashi-arasan, why don't we have a session at Sashiko?
This is interesting, isn't it?
It is indeed interesting.
Well, I'll buy about 500 yen, I've got money.
I'll buy a lot more.
I bought so much that I don't know what happened.
It's funny.
To the three-horse race, right?
Now, the 16th race is about to begin.
The first race of this time period will start immediately after leaving the pits, which is unique to Korea.
I seriously wonder what will happen.
We will start from the pit.
So you never know what will happen.
It's already started.
It starts from there.
I already bought a lot of things, but this time, I bought not 3 single clothes, but 3 series of clothes.
I bought five kinds of simple 3-series coverings.
I have extra money.
Oh, it's starting.
What do you mean, what's going to happen?
Oh, seriously.
Eh, seriously.
Seriously.
This is where you start, right?
I can't believe it.
Isn't it amazing? Two is good, two is good, two is good. Two is good, two is good. Not great? Two is good, two is good, two is good. Two is good, two is good.
Two is good. 2 is so good, isn't it?
Two is so good, isn't it? It's already a 2. It's two. It's two. It's totally two.
Oh, but 5 is good.
Two. Two, two, two. Two?
2? !
You've come this far and it's not 2?
What? What's coming?
4? No, but I still don't know. I don't know anything. I don't even know what I bought.
I mean, I was so sure it was a 2.
Four? - Two, three, six.
4, 2. 4, 2. 2 is here.
Really? Really?
Four, two, three, you're right.
I've got it. Four, two, three.
There it is. I got it.
I got it. I hit it.
That's good. Four.
Four... oh, which is it?
Yay! I won.
I wonder if it was popular. I wonder.
But I'm not in the 3-way betting range, but in the 3-way betting range.
Oh, single width? It's strong. Too strong.
Too strong.
Four, two, three, I won. Yay!
How popular were the four horses?
It's fun. It's fun to win, isn't it?
I didn't know how fun it was to win.
But it's amazing to hear that you're having fun even though you didn't want to win.
In the 16th race, I went to the wind to return the belly painting.Race 16, Wind went to return belly painting.
It's the favorite. I can't get it by the favorite.
What the heck, it's just a little bit more than last time.
Oh, no. It's that popular. Was it tickle lace?
Now, now, after the fitted panel.
Was it tickle lace? No way.
That's 1,750 yen.
1,750 yen back.
That was 2,500 yen.
Oh, it's a little bit tight.
Oh, no!
I'm screwed!
Well, I have an announcement to make to you all.
423, more popular than I thought it would be.
It came back more popular than I thought it would be.
1,700 yen
about
I bought the current race and it cost me 2,500 yen
Gami
The birth of the Klamath God!
Born in Korea!
I was a little bummed out.
If you think it's normal because it's 423
I'm so tickled and bummed.
Can you help me?
A human god...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hitojinshin just called.
There's one more race to go. The last race, there's one more race to go.
But even now... I won.
And I'm in the plus column.
I'm feeling good.
Otz is running away with it a little bit more.
Yeah, I don't know Otz at all.
But you know what?
This is really bad, isn't it? This start away from the pits.
I don't know what's going to happen.
But maybe it's just the order of popularity.
It's normal.
Oh, wow!
Wait, isn't there a sixth boat?
There are only five boats.
What?
Missing?
There's no boat 5. We're missing.
But boat 5 was the favorite. 17.
The absentee.
But the fifth boat...
It's going to lose money.
Why do you want to miss the 5th boat?
Because it's basic, and you want to hold on to it.
I've never had a good time.
You can do it at the end of the day. That's boat racing.
You can do whatever you want at the end.
There's a theory that the doublet is better than the doublet.
Oh, really?
Oh, the double-quadruple...Oh, the two-strike one.
It's on.
3 points at least often
First place.
Yes.
Some three-rounders are paid two points more often than three-rounders.
The two-triplets get paid more.
Does that happen?
I'm going for the hole, so here, come here.
I'll just buy two.
Lastly, I'm going to go with Shiboshibo.
Shiboshibo.
Here's my last race times.
I've come this far solidly in the shiboshibo.
I expect it will be solid in the future, too.
Er, 3 turn clothes
126, 122, 1,000 yen each
I bought
Uh, 1216, two stacks.
Ho
Hoang.
I'm going to go with the most popular two-stack off the top.
Wow, I bought 2,500 yen.
I really wanted to buy it for 5,000, 5,000 yen.
I made a mistake.
I see.
I just want to enjoy the last race.
I'm at ease now.
Oh, go!
Go!Go!
We've got 17 in a row.
Let's start 17 in a row!
Oh, that's one. That's one.
One more. One more.
One.
Wow, that's good!
Wow, don't eat the head of a four. It's a one, for sure.
This one.
Uh, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one.
okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Ew.
Wow. Three, huh?
Oh, no.
You got six pushes.
You got six!
Yeah, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Get off, get off, get off, get off.
oh, scary, scary, scary, scary, scary!
Uh-oh.
ohohoh...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
2 should come.
Aigo.
One changes?
One changes? What?
Is 4 a thing?
Wow, it's a rough race.
It was a rough race at the last minute.It was a rough race at the very end!
Wait a minute, 3 and 6 are already competing too hard!
Aigo.
What's "Aigo"?
416?
Wow, there's no way I'm going to guess.
One last thing.
Wait, everybody's leaving.
Everyone's leaving.
There it is.
But I put 6 in the third place because it was the last race.
I thought he'd come, so I put him in third place, six.
What a shame.
If it had been a three-horse race, it might have happened.
It's frustrating.
But I feel good about it.
Look.
Wow.
But if it's a triplet, does that mean I only get 3.6?
Impossible.
No, you can't do a 3-single.
Okay, I'll make an announcement.
Today, ladies and gentlemen, I'd like to show you something.
As of this moment.
We have 100,000 yen.
That's 10,000 won.
12345 plus 5. That's 100,000 won.
At this point, we have 10,000 won
And that's 42,600 won.And it was 42,600 won.
Plus I got a Korean mow dress
Thank you very much.
It's a miracle that I could go home with an extra 4,000 won, but I really had a great time today!
I definitely want to come back!
I really had a great time at the Equal Love Mode Race Club in Korea!
Thank you very much. I'm doing very well today, and I'm going home with 4,000 yen.
I'm going to use that 4,000 yen to go to Korea and eat some delicious food.
I think I'll go to Korea now and have a nice meal for 4,000 yen.
I'm going to return to Japan and work in the Ikolab Mode Race Club again.
So please keep your eyes on us!
And I hope that today's video has been of some help to Mode Race fans.
So thank you all for watching!
Bye bye!